<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Resume on Sarah Allen Reed, Goblin Queen.</title>
    <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Resume on Sarah Allen Reed, Goblin Queen.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bibliography</title>
      <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/bibliography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/bibliography/</guid>
      <description>The following is a semi-complete list of comix and sequential art projects I have contributed to, as well as relevant links.
If you are looking for an abbreviated history of my illustration work, please refer to the Selected Illustration Work page for a list of appearances. For sample illustration work that is not sequential art work, please see the Illustration sample page; for sequential art samples, please click on the &amp;ldquo;Sequential&amp;rdquo; link above, or click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discography</title>
      <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/discography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/discography/</guid>
      <description>Below is a short summary of my discography up to this point, with some singles omitted. For samples of these recordings, please refer to the Music link in the menu above, or check out my Bandcamp or my Soundcloud.
If you would like to hire me to produce a soundtrack for your game or film, or if your label would be interested in signing me, please click here.
as Ophelia Drowning  Ophelia Drowning And Idacarabus</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Illustration Clients</title>
      <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clients/</guid>
      <description>The following is a semi-complete list of companies and publications I have done illustration for, as well as relevant links.
If you are looking for an abbreviated history of my sequential art and comix work, please refer to the Bibliography section for a list of appearances.
For a wide range of examples of my abilities in regards to sequential art, please refer to the Sequential Art page in the navbar above; for illustration and fine art samples, please click on the &amp;ldquo;Illustration&amp;rdquo; link above, or click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Client Reviews</title>
      <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/pullquotes2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/pullquotes2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I hired Sarah to make the album art for my full-length, as well as a t-shirt design based off of that. Sarah conducted herself in a helpful and professional manner throughout the entire experience; the consultation and quotation process were smooth and informative, and gave me confidence in hiring her services. She was communicative every step of the way, showing me progress pictures and regularly asking for my input. Of course, my input was barely needed aside from the initial consultation; her artistic ability is unparalleled!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Peer Reviews</title>
      <link>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/pullquotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sarahallenreed.com/resume/pullquotes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Sarah is a sure-footed comics artist whose sense of DIY ethos and love of the medium have combined to make something powerful and beautiful and truly her own. The struggle is real, but with a pen in our hands, the artist will find glory at its peak. Sarah&amp;rsquo;s work marks the emergence of a new leader on the rise with enough energy to drill through the toughest obstacles with the sharp edge of printed media and the blunt power of comics culture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>