<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Selected Peer Reviews And Client Testimonials on Piper Bly, Goblin Queen.</title>
    <link>https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Selected Peer Reviews And Client Testimonials on Piper Bly, Goblin Queen.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Peer Reviews</title>
      <link>https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/pullquotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/pullquotes/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Piper is a sure-footed comics artist whose sense of DIY ethos and love of the medium have combined to make something powerful and beautiful and truly her own. The struggle is real, but with a pen in our hands, the artist will find glory at its peak. Piper&amp;rsquo;s work marks the emergence of a new leader on the rise with enough energy to drill through the toughest obstacles with the sharp edge of printed media and the blunt power of comics culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Client Reviews</title>
      <link>https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/pullquotes2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sarahallenreed.com/resume/clientreview/pullquotes2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I hired Piper to make the album art for my full-length, as well as a t-shirt design based off of that. Piper conducted herself in a helpful and professional manner throughout the entire experience; the consultation and quotation process were smooth and informative, and gave me confidence in hiring her services. She was communicative every step of the way, showing me progress pictures and regularly asking for my input. Of course, my input was barely needed aside from the initial consultation; her artistic ability is unparalleled!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>